{"data":[{"question":"In April 1984, David Hempleman - Adams walked through northern Canada to the North Pole with himself.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"walked","c":"to","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"- with-> by ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"David was a bravery man to go on this adventure by himself.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"bravery","c":"on","d":"himself","answer":"2","explain":"- Bravery->brave","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Biddenden, England is a small town of 1,500 person, with a history of nine hundred years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"of","c":"person","d":"hundred","answer":"3","explain":"- Person-> people","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Each Easter Monday, old people, widows, widowers, and others living on small incomes take part with a ceremony called Chulkurst Charity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"old","b":"living","c":"with","d":"called","answer":"3","explain":"- With-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Her family were patriots who supported the American Revolutional.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"patriots","c":"who","d":"Revolutional","answer":"4","explain":"- Evolutional-> revolution","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"She would be killed if that she did not betray the patriots in the area.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would","b":"if that","c":"did not","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"- If that-> if","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The city of Lufkin, Texas, has had much than ten million employees working for it without pay.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"city","b":"has had","c":"much","d":"working","answer":"3","explain":"- Much-> more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"These employers have not taken vacations, asked for sick leave, or complained about having to work long hours.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"employers","b":"taken","c":"asked","d":"having","answer":"1","explain":"- Employers-> employees","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The worms eat the waste and turn it into clean fertilizer whom the city then sells to farmers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"eat","b":"into","c":"whom","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"- Whom-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"During the Revolutionary War, American patriot wives and children frequently had to take refuge in forts escaping attacks.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"During","b":"wives","c":"take","d":"escaping","answer":"4","explain":"- Escaping-> to escape","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}